[
{"question": "How can you initialize chartboost for android?", "answers": []},
{"question": "android game programming pacman", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    hi s.oztrk,\r\n\r\nI think firstly u should research on how to recognize speech in Android.\r\nTry google with this keywords  \"\"\r\nI've found some good resources:\r\n[]\r\n[]\r\n\r\nHope they're useful for you.\r\nWebMaster4-Jan-13 17:31pm"]},
{"question": "Array in r.id.i[I]  android", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    As you can see from your calls to findViewById, you cannot use strings to reference resources, you must use the actual resource identifiers. So you could try something like:\r\nint[] Sellers = {r.id.seller1, r.id.seller2, r.id.seller3, r.id.seller4, ...};\r\n// and replace it in \r\nt[i] = (EditText) findViewById(Sellers[i]);But all of this begs the question: do you really need EditText types for this, or could a List<T> work better?\r\nRichard MacCutchan24-Sep-20 12:47pm24-Sep-20 16:50pm24-Sep-20 17:14pm", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    If you have fixed naming convention then code like below would be easier instead of defining an array with all IDs. \r\n\r\nTry:\r\nArrayList<EditText> myList = new ArrayList<EditText>();\r\n\r\n// Removed array\r\nString sellerID;\r\nint resourceViewID; \r\n\r\nfor (int i = 0; i < 4; i++)\r\n{\r\n   sellerID = \"seller\" + i;\r\n   resourceViewID = getResources().getIdentifier(sellerID, \"id\", getPackageName());\r\n   myList.add((EditText)findViewById(resourceViewID);\r\n}\r\nReference: [] \r\n\r\n24-Sep-20 16:56pmString24-Sep-20 17:12pm24-Sep-20 17:20pm"]},
{"question": "Array in r.id.i[I]  android", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    As you can see from your calls to findViewById, you cannot use strings to reference resources, you must use the actual resource identifiers. So you could try something like:\r\nint[] Sellers = {r.id.seller1, r.id.seller2, r.id.seller3, r.id.seller4, ...};\r\n// and replace it in \r\nt[i] = (EditText) findViewById(Sellers[i]);But all of this begs the question: do you really need EditText types for this, or could a List<T> work better?\r\nRichard MacCutchan24-Sep-20 12:47pm24-Sep-20 16:50pm24-Sep-20 17:14pm", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    If you have fixed naming convention then code like below would be easier instead of defining an array with all IDs. \r\n\r\nTry:\r\nArrayList<EditText> myList = new ArrayList<EditText>();\r\n\r\n// Removed array\r\nString sellerID;\r\nint resourceViewID; \r\n\r\nfor (int i = 0; i < 4; i++)\r\n{\r\n   sellerID = \"seller\" + i;\r\n   resourceViewID = getResources().getIdentifier(sellerID, \"id\", getPackageName());\r\n   myList.add((EditText)findViewById(resourceViewID);\r\n}\r\nReference: [] \r\n\r\n24-Sep-20 16:56pmString24-Sep-20 17:12pm24-Sep-20 17:20pm"]},
{"question": "Array in r.id.i[I]  android", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    As you can see from your calls to findViewById, you cannot use strings to reference resources, you must use the actual resource identifiers. So you could try something like:\r\nint[] Sellers = {r.id.seller1, r.id.seller2, r.id.seller3, r.id.seller4, ...};\r\n// and replace it in \r\nt[i] = (EditText) findViewById(Sellers[i]);But all of this begs the question: do you really need EditText types for this, or could a List<T> work better?\r\nRichard MacCutchan24-Sep-20 12:47pm24-Sep-20 16:50pm24-Sep-20 17:14pm", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    If you have fixed naming convention then code like below would be easier instead of defining an array with all IDs. \r\n\r\nTry:\r\nArrayList<EditText> myList = new ArrayList<EditText>();\r\n\r\n// Removed array\r\nString sellerID;\r\nint resourceViewID; \r\n\r\nfor (int i = 0; i < 4; i++)\r\n{\r\n   sellerID = \"seller\" + i;\r\n   resourceViewID = getResources().getIdentifier(sellerID, \"id\", getPackageName());\r\n   myList.add((EditText)findViewById(resourceViewID);\r\n}\r\nReference: [] \r\n\r\n24-Sep-20 16:56pmString24-Sep-20 17:12pm24-Sep-20 17:20pm"]},
{"question": "How to delete a file android", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Re: deleteOnExit()\r\n\r\n\r\nGerry Schmitz"]},
{"question": "Build mupdf for android", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    []\r\nRichard MacCutchan17-Mar-20 4:23am17-Mar-20 4:47am"]},
{"question": "How to open pdf file directly android", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    <?xml version=\"1.0\" encoding=\"utf-8\"?>\r\n<androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout xmlns:android=\"http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android\"\r\n    xmlns:tools=\"http://schemas.android.com/tools\"\r\n    android:layout_width=\"match_parent\"\r\n    android:layout_height=\"match_parent\"\r\n    tools:context=\".WebViewActivity\">\r\n\r\n    <WebView\r\n        android:id=\"@+id/webView\"\r\n        android:layout_width=\"match_parent\"\r\n        android:layout_height=\"match_parent\" />\r\n\r\n</androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>\r\nseotutorialszone"]},
{"question": "Android studio only shows one button! !", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Any XML attributes prefixed with tools are removed when the app is compiled and are only rendered by Android Studio layout editor.\r\n\r\nYou need to properly set constraints in your ConstraintLayout, not use absolute positioning.\r\n\r\nOr you may instead use RelativeLayout, LinearLayout, etc.\r\n\r\nThe problem is that your views are not properly constrained (basically they aren't linked to anything so when you run your app it doesn't know where to place them and just defaults to the upper left).\r\n\r\nSolution 1 - Right Click on you Layout and select \"Convert View\" Option. then select \"LinearLayout\" Option. it will show all three buttons in the output.\r\n\r\nOtherwise read about Constraints , once you use the guidelines, your buttons will display correctly.\r\n\r\nEDIT: As was rightly pointed out by David Crow, the width is set to the same as their parent causing buttons to overlap and lay on top of each other.\r\nAndre Oosthuizen7-Jul-20 8:15amConstraintLayout7-Jul-20 8:53am7-Jul-20 8:56am7-Jul-20 8:50am7-Jul-20 9:29am", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Bro u are unable to see ur buttons because u have given \"horizontal\" to ur android:orientation=\"Horizontal\"\r\nU just copy this code and paste it to ur xml file\r\n\r\n<?xml version=\"1.0\" encoding=\"utf-8\"?>\r\n\r\n<LinearLayout xmlns:android=\"http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android\"\r\n    xmlns:tools=\"http://schemas.android.com/tools\"\r\n    android:layout_width=\"match_parent\"\r\n    android:layout_height=\"match_parent\"\r\n    android:orientation=\"vertical\">\r\n\r\n    <Button\r\n        android:id=\"@+id/button3\"\r\n        style=\"?android:attr/borderlessButtonStyle\"\r\n        android:layout_width=\"match_parent\"\r\n        android:layout_height=\"wrap_content\"\r\n        android:text=\"strBtn3\" />\r\n\r\n    <Button\r\n        android:id=\"@+id/button2\"\r\n        style=\"?android:attr/borderlessButtonStyle\"\r\n        android:layout_width=\"match_parent\"\r\n        android:layout_height=\"wrap_content\"\r\n        android:text=\"strBtn2\" />\r\n\r\n    <Button\r\n        android:id=\"@+id/button1\"\r\n        style=\"?android:attr/borderlessButtonStyle\"\r\n        android:layout_width=\"match_parent\"\r\n        android:layout_height=\"wrap_content\"\r\n        android:text=\"strBtn1\" />\r\n    <Button\r\n        android:id=\"@+id/button4\"\r\n        style=\"?android:attr/borderlessButtonStyle\"\r\n        android:layout_width=\"match_parent\"\r\n        android:layout_height=\"wrap_content\"\r\n        android:text=\"strBtn4\" />\r\n</LinearLayout>\r\nMember 14883729"]},
{"question": "My android emulator (AVD) shut down automatically", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Solution.1 \r\nBy setting the  on the Android Virtual Device to  instead of  or . Once you did that the emulator device started up great and everything worked.\r\n Or\r\nGo to Menu->Tools->Android and uncheck the option Enable ADB Integration Run the application. Now the emulator will be launched, but app will not run. Once the emulator is fully launched, check the Enable ADB Integration option and re-run the app. Now the app will be launched in the already running emulator.\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nSolution.2\r\nYou might have forwarding enabled on adb. You can try this: Quit Android studio and launch terminal. Run these commands:\r\n\r\nadb \r\nadb \r\nadb  \r\nNow you can launch Android Studio and try again.\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nI hope one of the solution work for you.\r\nThank You!!!\r\nAshish Lovez22-May-17 11:15am24-May-17 9:02am", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Look like it exactly duplicate from []\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nUnchecking the Enable ADB Integration option and checking it back.\r\nIf this doesn't work, try another alternatives from []\r\n\r\nHope this help.\r\nwseng", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    I've installed and update of SDK - Android Emulator and it worked! hope solve it for you too\r\nMember 1496322013-Oct-20 9:23am"]},
{"question": "Vertical viewpager not working in kotlin android", "answers": []},
{"question": "App not working in ver4, 8 android where is the problem?", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    If this is related to an answer to a question, then you would need to post it to that solution, not start a new question. That way, the person who answered is sent an email that you have follow up information. Posting as a new question relies on them spotting it and realizing it's for them.\r\nBut since your user has no other questions listed, it's unlikely that it is.\r\n\r\nSo let's treat it as a \"new question\" instead. And we can't help you: we have no idea what your code looks like, how it works, what server you are trying to access, what \"does not log\" actually means, or any way to duplicate the problem, much less solve it for you.\r\n\r\nSo, it's going to be up to you.\r\nFortunately, you have a tool available to you which will help you find out what is going on: the debugger. How you use it depends on your compiler system, but a quick Google for the name of your IDE and \"debugger\" should give you the info you need.\r\n\r\nPut a breakpoint on the first line in the function, and run your code through the debugger. Then look at your code, and at your data and work out what should happen manually. Then single step each line checking that what you expected to happen is exactly what did. When it isn't, that's when you have a problem, and you can back-track (or run it again and look more closely) to find out why.\r\n\r\nSorry, but we can't do that for you - time for you to learn a new (and very, very useful) skill: debugging!\r\nOriginalGriff"]},
{"question": "Use an android device as an external dedicated GPU", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    What gives you the idea that the GPU on an Android device would be good enough for PC gaming?\r\n\r\nIt would be MUCH cheaper (by hundreds of dollars) to build a desktop box for gaming, than it would be to buy a laptop capable of decent gaming. Not only that, but it would almost infinitely upgradeable (CPU, RAM, and video card), where in a laptop, you are stuck with the CPU and video card that comes in it when you buy it.\r\n\r\nIf you insist on gaming with a laptop:\r\n\r\n0) Stop messing around and buy a decent laptop. Not only will it be \"good enough\" for work, but it would also be \"good enough\" for gaming.\r\n\r\n1) Buy one with as little RAM as possible and an analog hard drive, and upgrade those items yourself. It's much cheaper to do that.\r\n\r\n\r\nBuying advice - you want a laptop that supports:\r\n\r\n0) Up to 32GB DDR4 RAM\r\n1) nVME PCIx M2.2800 SSD - this is a MUCH faster SSD than a SATA SSD.\r\n2) A quad-core CPU (i7 or Ryzen).\r\n3) A decent video GPU. Check out \"gaming\" laptops to see what GPU they have, and then try to find a non-gaming laptop that has the same GPU. The word \"gaming\" adds a couple hundred dollars to the cost of the computer, so avoid them if possible.\r\n4) A 17-inch screen. Yes, 15's are somewhat lighter, but who cares.\r\n\r\nI recent bought a new (DELL) laptop with an 8th gen i7 quad core CPU, 8gb RAM, Radeon 530 GPU, and a 2TB analog sata drive. It cost almost $1000, but it's sufficient for most gaming you'd want to do on a laptop. I upgraded it to a 500GB nVME drive and 16GB RAM. I'm running Linux on it, but it came with Win10.\r\n\r\nI still think you should build a desktop box to game on, though.\r\n#realJSOP", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    First, this would be an EXTREMELY ADVANCED project to take on. It would required knowledge of the internals of DirectX, game rendering, Windows internals, Android internals, the hardware on both machines, and even USB. For someone with a \"(veeeeeerrrryyy basic)\" level of coding, this is a project that would take years of work.\r\n\r\nBasically, this isn't practical at all. The GPU in the phone cannot take on the loads imposed by PC games today. There's a reason why modern GPUs are backed by gigabytes of high speed memory and a PCIe bus. The amount of data being transferred over USB would just crush the interface. It just cannot keep up with the data transfer requirements of a GPU.\r\nDave Kreskowiak", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    sell yourphone and buy an external gpu problem solved\r\nMember 14960951", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    No. Your phone's GPU is in one chip with the CPU, some of the memory, and its display controller, and they're all tightly integrated together. Also, there'd be no way to connect it efficiently to the laptop. Only the latest generation of USB and Thunderbolt have enough bandwidth to be even worth considering for external GPUs, and even then, they're only used with dedicated hardware at the GPU end of the link - not a general-purpose processor. Apart from the fundamental problems, there's the very practical issue that your PC doesn't have any drivers for the GPU on the phone.\r\n\r\nOr you can spend a very long time making your own os and integrate drivers to do that. It is possible. It won't be a fun little project you can get over with in a summer break.\r\n\r\nYou can start by studying the basics of Drivers, DirectX, GPUs for laptops and phones... and so on\r\nThat is why it will take you pretty long to get it done.\r\nMember 14961699"]},
{"question": "Synchronizing Data base with Android application", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    I guess you can do by this way: \r\nAt server-side, you define some .\r\nAt Android application, you define servie that run in background, and invoke to those web servies in a interval you defined before.\r\nTo invoke web services from Android application, you can use open source lib named [] or JSON.\r\nWebMaster", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    if you using excel workbook by name then you must be use index of your excel workbook, by using it your issue should be resolved :)\r\nURVISH_SUTHAR1"]},
{"question": null, "answers": []},
{"question": "My android emulator (AVD) shut down automatically", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Solution.1 \r\nBy setting the  on the Android Virtual Device to  instead of  or . Once you did that the emulator device started up great and everything worked.\r\n Or\r\nGo to Menu->Tools->Android and uncheck the option Enable ADB Integration Run the application. Now the emulator will be launched, but app will not run. Once the emulator is fully launched, check the Enable ADB Integration option and re-run the app. Now the app will be launched in the already running emulator.\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nSolution.2\r\nYou might have forwarding enabled on adb. You can try this: Quit Android studio and launch terminal. Run these commands:\r\n\r\nadb \r\nadb \r\nadb  \r\nNow you can launch Android Studio and try again.\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nI hope one of the solution work for you.\r\nThank You!!!\r\nAshish Lovez22-May-17 11:15am24-May-17 9:02am", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Look like it exactly duplicate from []\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nUnchecking the Enable ADB Integration option and checking it back.\r\nIf this doesn't work, try another alternatives from []\r\n\r\nHope this help.\r\nwseng", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    I've installed and update of SDK - Android Emulator and it worked! hope solve it for you too\r\nMember 1496322013-Oct-20 9:23am"]},
{"question": "How to reterive the name of the uri android", "answers": []},
{"question": "How to set the path of downloaded file android", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Looks to me that you're calling your download manager in the wrong place.\r\n\r\n\r\nIntent intent = new Intent();\r\n       \r\nintent = getIntent();\r\n\r\n       \r\ncontactUri = intent.getData();\r\nUri src_uri = Uri.parse(contactUri.getPath()); \r\nUri dst_uri = Uri.parse(\"file:///mnt/sdcard/download/testing.pdf\");  \r\nDownloadManager.Request req = new DownloadManager.Request(src_uri);\r\nreq.setDestinationUri(dst_uri);\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\ntry this:\r\nIntent intent = new Intent();\r\nintent = getIntent();\r\n\r\n       contactUri = intent.getData();\r\nUri src_uri = Uri.parse(contactUri.getPath());\r\n   Uri dst_uri = Uri.parse(\"file:///mnt/sdcard/download/testing.pdf\");\r\n\r\nMember 14897805"]},
{"question": "How to share data using getintent() android", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    A similar query asked few yeas back at , snippet from there:\r\nThe string that you get from intent actually is the URI for the file. You can use this method to get the actual path:\r\npublic static String getActualPath(final Context context, final Uri uri) {\r\n\r\n    final boolean isKitKat = Build.VERSION.SDK_INT >= Build.VERSION_CODES.KITKAT;\r\n\r\n    // DocumentProvider\r\n    if (isKitKat && DocumentsContract.isDocumentUri(context, uri)) {\r\n        // ExternalStorageProvider\r\n        if (isExternalStorageDocument(uri)) {\r\n            final String docId = DocumentsContract.getDocumentId(uri);\r\n            final String[] split = docId.split(\":\");\r\n            final String type = split[0];\r\n\r\n            if (\"primary\".equalsIgnoreCase(type)) {\r\n                return Environment.getExternalStorageDirectory() + \"/\" + split[1];\r\n            }\r\n\r\n            // TODO handle non-primary volumes\r\n        }\r\n        // DownloadsProvider\r\n        else if (isDownloadsDocument(uri)) {\r\n\r\n            final String id = DocumentsContract.getDocumentId(uri);\r\n            final Uri contentUri = ContentUris.withAppendedId(\r\n                    Uri.parse(\"content://downloads/public_downloads\"), Long.valueOf(id));\r\n\r\n            return getDataColumn(context, contentUri, null, null);\r\n        }\r\n        // MediaProvider\r\n        else if (isMediaDocument(uri)) {\r\n            final String docId = DocumentsContract.getDocumentId(uri);\r\n            final String[] split = docId.split(\":\");\r\n            final String type = split[0];\r\n\r\n            Uri contentUri = null;\r\n            if (\"image\".equals(type)) {\r\n                contentUri = MediaStore.Images.Media.EXTERNAL_CONTENT_URI;\r\n            } else if (\"video\".equals(type)) {\r\n                contentUri = MediaStore.Video.Media.EXTERNAL_CONTENT_URI;\r\n            } else if (\"audio\".equals(type)) {\r\n                contentUri = MediaStore.Audio.Media.EXTERNAL_CONTENT_URI;\r\n            }\r\n\r\n            final String selection = \"_id=?\";\r\n            final String[] selectionArgs = new String[] {\r\n                    split[1]\r\n            };\r\n\r\n            return getDataColumn(context, contentUri, selection, selectionArgs);\r\n        }\r\n    }\r\n    // MediaStore (and general)\r\n    else if (\"content\".equalsIgnoreCase(uri.getScheme())) {\r\n        return getDataColumn(context, uri, null, null);\r\n    }\r\n    // File\r\n    else if (\"file\".equalsIgnoreCase(uri.getScheme())) {\r\n        return uri.getPath();\r\n    }\r\n\r\n    return null;\r\n}\r\nModify and use as per your need.\r\n"]},
{"question": "How to set the path of downloaded file android", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Looks to me that you're calling your download manager in the wrong place.\r\n\r\n\r\nIntent intent = new Intent();\r\n       \r\nintent = getIntent();\r\n\r\n       \r\ncontactUri = intent.getData();\r\nUri src_uri = Uri.parse(contactUri.getPath()); \r\nUri dst_uri = Uri.parse(\"file:///mnt/sdcard/download/testing.pdf\");  \r\nDownloadManager.Request req = new DownloadManager.Request(src_uri);\r\nreq.setDestinationUri(dst_uri);\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\ntry this:\r\nIntent intent = new Intent();\r\nintent = getIntent();\r\n\r\n       contactUri = intent.getData();\r\nUri src_uri = Uri.parse(contactUri.getPath());\r\n   Uri dst_uri = Uri.parse(\"file:///mnt/sdcard/download/testing.pdf\");\r\n\r\nMember 14897805"]},
{"question": "Android Trainee", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Just google 'future of Android Technology', lots of articles discussing all the different points of view\r\n\r\n[]\r\n\r\n[]\r\n\r\nGenerally seems to be quite a positive outlook. \r\n\r\n[]\r\n\r\nOlder graph, but projections for 2012 are high\r\n\r\n[]\r\nDylan Morley", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    hi \r\n\r\nAndroid is the future technology for mobile applications.\r\n\r\n\r\nsee link \r\n[]\r\nsam_ckp"]},
{"question": "Android Advertising", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    The question is what your advertising looks like? Let's suppose you want to download some new info to be shown from web. To read text you can use something like:\r\nInputStream is = null;\r\ntry {\r\n    is = OpenHttpConnection(URL);\r\n    InputStreamReader isr = new InputStreamReader(is);\r\n    int read;\r\n    String str = \"\";\r\n    char[] ib = new char[1024];\r\n\r\n   while ((read = isr.read(ib))>0)\r\n   {\r\n     String string =\r\n     String.copyValueOf(ib, 0, read);\r\n     str += string;\r\n     ib = new char[1024];\r\n  }\r\n   in.close();\r\n} catch (Exception e) {\r\n}\r\n\r\n\r\nFor images BitmapFactory has decodeStream method.\r\nAnd finally use Toast to show your ads. It can be quite complicated, if you provide corresponding layout for it. Design your layout to have all info needed and show the toast:\r\n\r\nToast toast = new Toast(getApplicationContext());\r\ntoast.setGarvity(Gravity.LEFT | Gravity.BOTTOM, 0, 0);\r\ntoast.setDuration(Toast.LENGTH_LONG);\r\ntoast.setView(layout);\r\ntoast.show();\r\n\r\nIgor Kushnarev22-Nov-10 4:21am"]},
{"question": "dictonary in android", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    I think the Android SDK itself has a Dictionary example. I have gone through the code two months back.\r\n\r\n[]\r\n\r\n[]\r\ndavidshenba", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Thanks very much , I will go through it\r\nhozifa"]},
{"question": "Android Trainee", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Just google 'future of Android Technology', lots of articles discussing all the different points of view\r\n\r\n[]\r\n\r\n[]\r\n\r\nGenerally seems to be quite a positive outlook. \r\n\r\n[]\r\n\r\nOlder graph, but projections for 2012 are high\r\n\r\n[]\r\nDylan Morley", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    hi \r\n\r\nAndroid is the future technology for mobile applications.\r\n\r\n\r\nsee link \r\n[]\r\nsam_ckp"]},
{"question": "Print pdf from android direct to epson", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    See []\r\nRichard MacCutchan23-May-20 17:31pm24-May-20 3:58am25-May-20 11:51am25-May-20 11:59am"]},
{"question": "How to upload video to server android app", "answers": []},
{"question": "How to share data using getintent() android", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    A similar query asked few yeas back at , snippet from there:\r\nThe string that you get from intent actually is the URI for the file. You can use this method to get the actual path:\r\npublic static String getActualPath(final Context context, final Uri uri) {\r\n\r\n    final boolean isKitKat = Build.VERSION.SDK_INT >= Build.VERSION_CODES.KITKAT;\r\n\r\n    // DocumentProvider\r\n    if (isKitKat && DocumentsContract.isDocumentUri(context, uri)) {\r\n        // ExternalStorageProvider\r\n        if (isExternalStorageDocument(uri)) {\r\n            final String docId = DocumentsContract.getDocumentId(uri);\r\n            final String[] split = docId.split(\":\");\r\n            final String type = split[0];\r\n\r\n            if (\"primary\".equalsIgnoreCase(type)) {\r\n                return Environment.getExternalStorageDirectory() + \"/\" + split[1];\r\n            }\r\n\r\n            // TODO handle non-primary volumes\r\n        }\r\n        // DownloadsProvider\r\n        else if (isDownloadsDocument(uri)) {\r\n\r\n            final String id = DocumentsContract.getDocumentId(uri);\r\n            final Uri contentUri = ContentUris.withAppendedId(\r\n                    Uri.parse(\"content://downloads/public_downloads\"), Long.valueOf(id));\r\n\r\n            return getDataColumn(context, contentUri, null, null);\r\n        }\r\n        // MediaProvider\r\n        else if (isMediaDocument(uri)) {\r\n            final String docId = DocumentsContract.getDocumentId(uri);\r\n            final String[] split = docId.split(\":\");\r\n            final String type = split[0];\r\n\r\n            Uri contentUri = null;\r\n            if (\"image\".equals(type)) {\r\n                contentUri = MediaStore.Images.Media.EXTERNAL_CONTENT_URI;\r\n            } else if (\"video\".equals(type)) {\r\n                contentUri = MediaStore.Video.Media.EXTERNAL_CONTENT_URI;\r\n            } else if (\"audio\".equals(type)) {\r\n                contentUri = MediaStore.Audio.Media.EXTERNAL_CONTENT_URI;\r\n            }\r\n\r\n            final String selection = \"_id=?\";\r\n            final String[] selectionArgs = new String[] {\r\n                    split[1]\r\n            };\r\n\r\n            return getDataColumn(context, contentUri, selection, selectionArgs);\r\n        }\r\n    }\r\n    // MediaStore (and general)\r\n    else if (\"content\".equalsIgnoreCase(uri.getScheme())) {\r\n        return getDataColumn(context, uri, null, null);\r\n    }\r\n    // File\r\n    else if (\"file\".equalsIgnoreCase(uri.getScheme())) {\r\n        return uri.getPath();\r\n    }\r\n\r\n    return null;\r\n}\r\nModify and use as per your need.\r\n"]},
{"question": "Fetch data from sqlite and display activity 2 in android studio", "answers": []},
{"question": "How does android knows whihc broadcastreceiver to call ?", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    It is all explained in the documentation: [].\r\nRichard MacCutchan"]},
{"question": "java.net.UnknownHostException in android", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Not enough information, but\u2026 you cannot just \"fix\" it. You are doing something with the host address/name which does not actually exist. It could be host name not prescribed in DNS, something like that.\r\n\r\n\r\nSergey Alexandrovich Kryukov4-May-15 1:30am4-May-15 1:55am4-May-15 2:18am"]},
{"question": "Developing for android", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    check this:\r\n\r\n[]\r\nTorstenH."]},
{"question": "Can you please list me all the necessary things I should learn in android , to become an advanced  or atleast good with building android apps ?", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    See [].\r\nRichard MacCutchan", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Sorry, but we can't - not because we don't want to, or there is a rule against it, but simply there is no \"set level\" or \"curriculum\" for progressing from \"beginner\" to intermediate.\r\n\r\nIt's all down to experience, not \"book learning\" - though learning is a big part of it, it's learning skills rather than \"touching topics\".\r\n\r\nThink of some app project that would both interest and challenge you, and try to implement it. When it's working and you're happy, do it again with a couple of different apps. Design and write the the whole thing yourself - don;t copy'n'paste from SO or CP!\r\nThen go back to the first one and do it again from scratch - this time, using the skills and knowledge you've gained, and compare that code with your first try. Repeat for the other apps, and then run through again. You'll see what I mean!\r\n\r\nThere is no shortcut to this: learning the parts you have to play with is important, yes - but only part of the story, and a fairly small part compared with knowing how to use them efficiently, and what to use where.\r\n\r\nGood luck!\r\nOriginalGriff"]},
{"question": "TimerTask in Android", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Try this:\r\npublic class TicketFinalActivity extends Activity {\r\n\r\n    private final int DELAY_TIME = 1000;\r\n\r\n    @Override\r\n    protected void onCreate(Bundle savedInstanceState) {\r\n        super.onCreate(savedInstanceState);\r\n        setContentView(R.layout.main);\r\n\r\n        new Timer().schedule(new TimerTask() {\r\n            @Override\r\n            public void run() {\r\n                try {\r\n                    Intent i= new Intent(TicketFinalActivity.this, Caution.class);\r\n                    startActivity(i);\r\n                }\r\n                catch (Exception e) {\r\n                    Log.i(\"TAG\", \"Error: \" + e.getMessage());\r\n                    finish();\r\n                }\r\n            }\r\n        }, DELAY_TIME);\r\n    }\r\nBun Leap_kh2-Jul-12 3:39am2-Jul-12 3:41am"]},
{"question": null, "answers": []},
{"question": "java.net.UnknownHostException in android", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Not enough information, but\u2026 you cannot just \"fix\" it. You are doing something with the host address/name which does not actually exist. It could be host name not prescribed in DNS, something like that.\r\n\r\n\r\nSergey Alexandrovich Kryukov4-May-15 1:30am4-May-15 1:55am4-May-15 2:18am"]},
{"question": null, "answers": []},
{"question": "Orientation in Android", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    To enable the data for the angle, you have to write a certain Eventlistener and have to register it with the SensorManager class.\r\n\r\n\r\npublic class myAngleClass extends Activity\r\n{   \r\n    \r\n    public void onCreate(Bundle savedInstanceState)\r\n    {\r\n        super.onCreate(savedInstanceState);\r\n        setContentView(R.layout.main);        \r\n\r\n        SensorManager Manager = (SensorManager)\r\nthis.getSystemService(SENSOR_SERVICE);        \r\n\r\n        final float[] mValuesMagnet      = new float[3];\r\n        final float[] mValuesAccel       = new float[3];\r\n        final float[] mValuesOrientation = new float[3];\r\n        final float[] mRotationMatrix    = new float[9];\r\n\r\n       \r\n        final SensorEventListener mEventListener = new SensorEventListener() {\r\n            public void onAccuracyChanged(Sensor sensor, int accuracy) {\r\n            }\r\n\r\n            public void onSensorChanged(SensorEvent event) {\r\n               \r\n                switch (event.sensor.getType()) {\r\n                    case Sensor.TYPE_ACCELEROMETER:\r\n                        System.arraycopy(event.values, 0, mValuesAccel, 0, 3);\r\n                        break;\r\n\r\n                    case Sensor.TYPE_MAGNETIC_FIELD:\r\n                        System.arraycopy(event.values, 0, mValuesMagnet, 0, 3);\r\n                        break;\r\n                }\r\n            };\r\n        };\r\n\r\n// Register the event listener\r\n    public void regListeners(SensorManager Manager , SensorEventListener list)\r\n    {\r\n       Manager \r\n             .registerListener(list, Manager  \r\n             .getDefaultSensor(Sensor.TYPE_ACCELEROMETER), \r\n                SensorManager.SENSOR_DELAY_NORMAL);\r\n\r\n\r\n        Manager\r\n              .registerListener(list, \r\n               sensorManager.getDefaultSensor(Sensor.TYPE_MAGNETIC_FIELD), \r\n                SensorManager.SENSOR_DELAY_NORMAL);\r\n\r\n    }\r\n}\r\nexposed12"]},
{"question": "Recyclebin in android", "answers": []},
{"question": "Phonetic on Android?", "answers": []},
{"question": "AsyncTask in android", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    No, it is not needed to kill or terminate an asyncTask in any way, it should be garbage collected upon job finish (and send/retrieve the results back from the main thread via onPostExecute).\r\n\r\nI've used asyncTask to download thumbnails for lists over 1000 elements long, and never had a problem.\r\n\r\nHowever, it is a good practice to implement onCancelled method, and handle whatever it is the asyncTask is/was doing when cancelled (i.e. you have a download in progress, and the user cancels the download. What do you do then?)\r\n5-Sep-12 0:49am5-Sep-12 2:05am"]},
{"question": "TimerTask in Android", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Try this:\r\npublic class TicketFinalActivity extends Activity {\r\n\r\n    private final int DELAY_TIME = 1000;\r\n\r\n    @Override\r\n    protected void onCreate(Bundle savedInstanceState) {\r\n        super.onCreate(savedInstanceState);\r\n        setContentView(R.layout.main);\r\n\r\n        new Timer().schedule(new TimerTask() {\r\n            @Override\r\n            public void run() {\r\n                try {\r\n                    Intent i= new Intent(TicketFinalActivity.this, Caution.class);\r\n                    startActivity(i);\r\n                }\r\n                catch (Exception e) {\r\n                    Log.i(\"TAG\", \"Error: \" + e.getMessage());\r\n                    finish();\r\n                }\r\n            }\r\n        }, DELAY_TIME);\r\n    }\r\nBun Leap_kh2-Jul-12 3:39am2-Jul-12 3:41am"]},
{"question": "Android application for epilepsy", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    We do not do your homework: it is set for a reason. It is there so that you think about what you have been told, and try to understand it. It is also there so that your tutor can identify areas where you are weak, and focus more attention on remedial action.\r\n\r\nTry it yourself, you may find it is not as difficult as you think!\r\nOriginalGriff23-May-14 12:26pm"]},
{"question": "Localization In Android", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    []\r\n[]\r\nPrerak  Patel"]},
{"question": "An Android Application", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Your original question ([]), did not mention that you were interested in Android. However, the answer is still the same: use Java SE and work through the tutorials. When you feel comfortable with Java you can go to [] and learn Android programming.\r\n\r\nAlternatively, with your C# background, you could go to [] and use that framework.\r\nRichard MacCutchan"]},
{"question": "Android Sensor", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    You have to take into account acceleration due to gravity.  This will always be measured in a device with at least three orthogonal accelerometers.\r\n\r\nTo account for this, you have to have some sort of calibration where you put the device in a known orientation and make note of the accelerometer readings.  Then when using the device, you calculate the rotation and translation between the current sensor readings and the ones from the calibration to determine movement and orientation.\r\nKythen", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Meaning? So what I should do if there's no movement detected? What should I use instead?\r\nSmaini Nurbs", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    How do I go about doing this? What can I do then?\r\nSmaini Nurbs30-Nov-10 3:58am30-Nov-10 13:53pm"]},
{"question": "Webservice with android", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    I suggest you stop and think about exactly what you are trying to do. Do you want to manage some communication, switching TSQL commands? Do you want to create a webservice? Do you want to work with email? In whichever choice you make you will need to do some research into Android programming, so start here: []\r\nRichard MacCutchan"]},
{"question": "WebServices in Android", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Start here : []\r\nMehdi Gholam23-Aug-12 2:38am23-Aug-12 2:42am23-Aug-12 2:38am", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Lots of links you can get [], and the first result of this search is the link provided by Mehdi which will surely help you lot.\r\n\r\nGet some more similar threads on []\r\nPrasad_Kulkarni", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    System requires\r\n\r\nto make webservice Visual Studio or any you wish to made in \r\nServer IIS for .net , in case of php , java yo can use apache\r\n(Server basically creates bridge to connect services)\r\nIn case of databse your choice like sql server\r\nAnd for android side you will required ksoap jar file(you will get easily).\r\nAndroidVivek24-Aug-12 1:50am"]},
{"question": "WebServices in Android", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Start here : []\r\nMehdi Gholam23-Aug-12 2:38am23-Aug-12 2:42am23-Aug-12 2:38am", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Lots of links you can get [], and the first result of this search is the link provided by Mehdi which will surely help you lot.\r\n\r\nGet some more similar threads on []\r\nPrasad_Kulkarni", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    System requires\r\n\r\nto make webservice Visual Studio or any you wish to made in \r\nServer IIS for .net , in case of php , java yo can use apache\r\n(Server basically creates bridge to connect services)\r\nIn case of databse your choice like sql server\r\nAnd for android side you will required ksoap jar file(you will get easily).\r\nAndroidVivek24-Aug-12 1:50am"]},
{"question": "Android Trainee", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Just google 'future of Android Technology', lots of articles discussing all the different points of view\r\n\r\n[]\r\n\r\n[]\r\n\r\nGenerally seems to be quite a positive outlook. \r\n\r\n[]\r\n\r\nOlder graph, but projections for 2012 are high\r\n\r\n[]\r\nDylan Morley", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    hi \r\n\r\nAndroid is the future technology for mobile applications.\r\n\r\n\r\nsee link \r\n[]\r\nsam_ckp"]},
{"question": "Android or Windows 7", "answers": []},
{"question": "Developing for android", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    check this:\r\n\r\n[]\r\nTorstenH."]},
{"question": "Synchronizaton in Android", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Here's an [].\r\nNagy Vilmos1-Dec-10 9:12am1-Dec-10 9:23am"]},
{"question": "Android emulator don't fit the layout", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Hi Janna Mamer Dela Cruz,\r\n\r\nWas you emulator dont show your desired layout ?\r\nCheck again on onCreate() method of your Activity\r\n\r\npublic class Your_Activity extends Activity{\r\n\t\r\n\t@Override\r\n    public void onCreate(Bundle savedInstanceState) {\r\n        super.onCreate(savedInstanceState);\r\n        \r\n        // check here carefully.\r\n        setContentView(R.layout.your_desired_layout);\r\n    }\r\n\r\nOne more point, check whether your desired layout was set to layout.\r\nCheck in your AndroidManifest.xml file.\r\nMain activity ( which be started at first when application is run ) has below property:\r\n<intent-filter>\r\n\t<action android:name=\"android.intent.action.MAIN\" xmlns:android=\"#unknown\" />\r\n</intent-filter>\r\nWebMaster"]},
{"question": "Use an android device as an external dedicated GPU", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    What gives you the idea that the GPU on an Android device would be good enough for PC gaming?\r\n\r\nIt would be MUCH cheaper (by hundreds of dollars) to build a desktop box for gaming, than it would be to buy a laptop capable of decent gaming. Not only that, but it would almost infinitely upgradeable (CPU, RAM, and video card), where in a laptop, you are stuck with the CPU and video card that comes in it when you buy it.\r\n\r\nIf you insist on gaming with a laptop:\r\n\r\n0) Stop messing around and buy a decent laptop. Not only will it be \"good enough\" for work, but it would also be \"good enough\" for gaming.\r\n\r\n1) Buy one with as little RAM as possible and an analog hard drive, and upgrade those items yourself. It's much cheaper to do that.\r\n\r\n\r\nBuying advice - you want a laptop that supports:\r\n\r\n0) Up to 32GB DDR4 RAM\r\n1) nVME PCIx M2.2800 SSD - this is a MUCH faster SSD than a SATA SSD.\r\n2) A quad-core CPU (i7 or Ryzen).\r\n3) A decent video GPU. Check out \"gaming\" laptops to see what GPU they have, and then try to find a non-gaming laptop that has the same GPU. The word \"gaming\" adds a couple hundred dollars to the cost of the computer, so avoid them if possible.\r\n4) A 17-inch screen. Yes, 15's are somewhat lighter, but who cares.\r\n\r\nI recent bought a new (DELL) laptop with an 8th gen i7 quad core CPU, 8gb RAM, Radeon 530 GPU, and a 2TB analog sata drive. It cost almost $1000, but it's sufficient for most gaming you'd want to do on a laptop. I upgraded it to a 500GB nVME drive and 16GB RAM. I'm running Linux on it, but it came with Win10.\r\n\r\nI still think you should build a desktop box to game on, though.\r\n#realJSOP", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    First, this would be an EXTREMELY ADVANCED project to take on. It would required knowledge of the internals of DirectX, game rendering, Windows internals, Android internals, the hardware on both machines, and even USB. For someone with a \"(veeeeeerrrryyy basic)\" level of coding, this is a project that would take years of work.\r\n\r\nBasically, this isn't practical at all. The GPU in the phone cannot take on the loads imposed by PC games today. There's a reason why modern GPUs are backed by gigabytes of high speed memory and a PCIe bus. The amount of data being transferred over USB would just crush the interface. It just cannot keep up with the data transfer requirements of a GPU.\r\nDave Kreskowiak", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    sell yourphone and buy an external gpu problem solved\r\nMember 14960951", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    No. Your phone's GPU is in one chip with the CPU, some of the memory, and its display controller, and they're all tightly integrated together. Also, there'd be no way to connect it efficiently to the laptop. Only the latest generation of USB and Thunderbolt have enough bandwidth to be even worth considering for external GPUs, and even then, they're only used with dedicated hardware at the GPU end of the link - not a general-purpose processor. Apart from the fundamental problems, there's the very practical issue that your PC doesn't have any drivers for the GPU on the phone.\r\n\r\nOr you can spend a very long time making your own os and integrate drivers to do that. It is possible. It won't be a fun little project you can get over with in a summer break.\r\n\r\nYou can start by studying the basics of Drivers, DirectX, GPUs for laptops and phones... and so on\r\nThat is why it will take you pretty long to get it done.\r\nMember 14961699"]},
{"question": "Android NDK and Android SDK", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    The NDK is designed to enable you to create C++ libraries using the libc and libm libraries, along with native access to OpenGL.  If your inclinations run toward NDK development, exploring the Linux kernel  and C/C++ underbelly of Android, modifying Dalvik, or otherwise tinkering with things under the hood, For moer detials see this article . \r\n\r\n[]\r\n\r\nand if you want to begin devlop an android application see this article  : []\r\nAnas Al Salool", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Nope, you may (and probably ) use the SDK. \r\nSee the \"\" section of the \r\n[] page.\r\nCPallini1-Apr-11 3:25am", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    In addition to the Software Development Kit (SDK), which was released a couple months ago, the Android team has now also released a \"Native Development Kit\" (NDK). The SDK allows developers to write software for Android devices in Java. The system is designed for platform independence, so that no or little adjustments are required to run the same applications on different devices. The NDK on the other hand enables Andoid developers to access native code, which in general is not platform independent, but may be more efficient in some cases. More details and download information for the SDK and NDK is available at the Android web site.\r\nHope it helps you.\r\n\r\n\r\nAPPY CODING :-)\r\nAditya_Pandey"]},
{"question": "Alternative for synchronous retrofit2 in android java", "answers": []},
{"question": "How to use piccaso onitemselected in android", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    See []\r\nRichard MacCutchan"]},
{"question": "LayoutParams in Android", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Go and read []. You will be amazed at what you can learn.\r\nRichard MacCutchan"]},
{"question": "How to evauluate a numeric expression in android java ?", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    So basically, you have to write a calculator, and you don't want to do the \"difficult bit\" that you might learn something useful from?\r\n\r\nYou could try this: [] \r\n\r\nBut ... be aware that not only will you learn nothing useful from this assignment, but you will almost certainly get a poor grade as well: teachers can tell when you copy'n'paste a solution instead of \"rolling your own\" ...\r\n\r\nI'd strongly suggest that you look at writing a parser to check the expression syntax and build an execution tree or RPN stack while it's doing it for evaluation when it's shown to be valid. Then execute the tree / stack to produce your result. You will learn a whole load more about how to do things, and if your aim is to become and advanced Java programmer as you said two weeks ago then you need to actually practice writing code: []\r\nJuist grabbing somebody else's code, finding it doesn't work in your app for some reason, and abandoning it isn't a good way to get anywhere towards that goal.\r\nOriginalGriff30-Jul-20 8:23am30-Jul-20 22:41pm"]},
{"question": "Android's super folder for windows 10", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    I know of none, but this is not a development question, and this is a dev site: you need to try somewhere dedicated to the OS rather than creating software.\r\n\r\nTry here for starters: [] \r\nBut google will find you many more.\r\nOriginalGriff", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Maybe this one: []\r\nRickZeeland"]},
{"question": "Android project of my android", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    No. Why do you think we would give you the \"complete code for MY application\"? This is not a site where we do your homework / job for free.\r\nOriginalGriff", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    I see from all the \"please post the complete code\" school is back in :-)\r\nDarren_vms"]},
{"question": "how to learn android", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Start with the 12 winning articles from the recent [].\r\nPeter Leow5-Nov-14 7:20am5-Nov-14 19:50pm5-Nov-14 11:06am5-Nov-14 19:50pm"]},
{"question": "Uploading image in android to database without encoding", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    \r\nYou cannot remove it. For large data like image, you need to pass this using Request Body. HTTP uses the byte format of the data in the body.\r\n\r\nYou think you are not using it but is needed. Protocols convert it.  \r\n\r\nAdd on: A sample for your reference: []\r\n"]},
{"question": "Loop date not sorted (android studio)", "answers": []},
{"question": "accelerometer on android", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    You  can't: please see the following thread at 'The Competitors' website: [].\r\nCPallini25-Jan-12 17:11pm25-Jan-12 17:31pm25-Jan-12 17:33pm25-Jan-12 17:39pm", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    I can add some explanation to the correct answer by CPallini.\r\n\r\nTo acceleration is the second derivative of the coordinate and the only measurable characteristic of motion. According to Galilean relativity principle, it is impossible to tell the difference between coordinate systems moving with different speeds and having different reference point using any mechanical measurements. According to Einstein, no physical phenomena can be used to tell that, please see:\r\n[],\r\n[].\r\n\r\nIt is theoretically possible to estimate the displacement (and thus coordinates in case initial coordinate are known) of a device by measurement of the acceleration, but it needs permanent double integration of the acceleration (again, acceleration is the second derivative of the coordinates). It is quite apparent that all the errors tend to accumulate during integration. And any accelerometer is a device with inherent accuracy limitations: one can put it under conditions (certain vibration frequencies and accelerations) which could cause fatal loss of accuracy.\r\n\r\nThere is a very important technical problem here: the measurement and integration should be performed non-stop with regular time intervals which should never exceed some maximum sample rate. In other words, the computing system should be required to be a  or near real-time. I don't think Android is anything close to such system. Also, I'm not sure the device's accelerometer is a true 3D sensor.\r\n\r\nPlease see:\r\n[],\r\n[].\r\n\r\nNevertheless, such problem is successfully solved in rocket science. But motion in open space is much, much smoother and simpler than on the Earth. I would say, on Earth this problem is nearly hopeless.\r\n\r\n\r\nSergey Alexandrovich Kryukov25-Jan-12 17:34pm25-Jan-12 17:39pm26-Jan-12 3:18am26-Jan-12 3:25am26-Jan-12 7:03am26-Jan-12 11:36am", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    I've done this before on earth and in rocketry. \r\n\r\nEarth bound, best I saw was a robot at Draper labs, cambridge. They had errors of a few cm without GPS after tens of minutes.\r\nMuch better gyros, accelerometers, and timing than on a phone.\r\n\r\nOutdoors in good weather, it's easier to use GPS and filter to get submeter than using the accelerometers.\r\n\r\nThe inherent problems are: the sensor has noise, non-linearity and bias, AND you can't sample it fast enough or with good enough time precision.\r\nThat doesn't mean it can't be solved but it's hard :)\r\n\r\nLooking at 1 senor say the acceleration going left/right, we'll call that \"X\".\r\nNote how \"x\" real value is very different from the measured:\r\n\r\nXmeasured = bias + guassianNoise + a0*x + a1*x^2 + a2*x^3 + a3*x^3 ...\r\n\r\nWhere a0 is almost 1, and a1 - an are nearly (not quite) zero, but for most applications you could treat them as zero.\r\nThe bias (minor drift over temperature) is somewhat fixed and you can find it for a particular sensors datasheet, but its small but not zero.\r\n\r\nYou can use low pass / high pass filters to reject noise and the bias (respectively), or Kalman filter estimate the bias comparing it to GPS over a few minutes, but neither work very well (I've tried).\r\n\r\nWhen you integrate, you end up integrating all those errors. Very small things cause meters of error.\r\n\r\nAlso when you rotate the phone, you rotate your coordinate system so finding the updated GPS position or location in a room is also compounded by the gyroscope errors AND how the gyroscope / magnetometer updates.\r\n\r\nSo many errors, so many years to fix it :)\r\n\r\nThis is a fantastic problem to try to solve, so please don't be completely discouraged, but it's not something you can do in a weekend.\r\n\r\nRocket science is easier, but this is a great problem to solve, one I've spent some time on. Lots of fun.\r\n\r\nGood luck :)\r\nHoshiKata19-Dec-16 16:44pm"]},
{"question": "How to change android listview position after filtering for setonitemclicklistener", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    The position in onItemClick is an index of the adapter, e.g.\r\nadapter.getItemAtPosition(position)\r\nHowever you use it as an index for mapPost. It looks like you are filtering the adapter, but not mapPost.\r\nUser 7429338"]},
{"question": "Multiple post in android with multiple edittext", "answers": []},
{"question": "How to connect C# desktop app to android app", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    See: []\r\nRickZeeland"]},
{"question": "Uploading image in android to database without encoding", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    \r\nYou cannot remove it. For large data like image, you need to pass this using Request Body. HTTP uses the byte format of the data in the body.\r\n\r\nYou think you are not using it but is needed. Protocols convert it.  \r\n\r\nAdd on: A sample for your reference: []\r\n"]},
{"question": "Save house location ( android studio )", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    We are more than willing to help those that are stuck: but that doesn't mean that we are here to do it all for you! We can't do all the work, you are either getting paid for this, or it's part of your grades and it wouldn't be at all fair for us to do it all for you.\r\n\r\nSo we need you to do the work, and we will help you when you get stuck. That doesn't mean we will give you a step by step solution you can hand in!\r\nStart by explaining where you are at the moment, and what the next step in the process is. Then tell us what you have tried to get that next step working, and what happened when you did.\r\n\r\nIf you are having problems getting started at all, then this may help: []\r\nOriginalGriff"]},
{"question": "Display of MS documents on Android", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Hi sistlachetan,\r\n\r\nI think firstly, u should catch up how can  with  files.\r\nFor this point, I recommend reserching on []\r\n\r\n\r\nWebMaster"]},
{"question": "WebServices in Android", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Start here : []\r\nMehdi Gholam23-Aug-12 2:38am23-Aug-12 2:42am23-Aug-12 2:38am", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Lots of links you can get [], and the first result of this search is the link provided by Mehdi which will surely help you lot.\r\n\r\nGet some more similar threads on []\r\nPrasad_Kulkarni", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    System requires\r\n\r\nto make webservice Visual Studio or any you wish to made in \r\nServer IIS for .net , in case of php , java yo can use apache\r\n(Server basically creates bridge to connect services)\r\nIn case of databse your choice like sql server\r\nAnd for android side you will required ksoap jar file(you will get easily).\r\nAndroidVivek24-Aug-12 1:50am"]},
{"question": "Android crash when connecting to sqlite?", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    The only thing that would happen in the app you've shown is that the Main Activity would load and display something due to the OnCreate being called:\r\n\r\nprotected void onCreate(Bundle savedInstanceState) {\r\n        super.onCreate(savedInstanceState);\r\n        setContentView(R.layout.activity_main);\r\n    }\r\n\r\nSince OnCreate() only calls the setContentView() and nothing else, then none of the methods you show below that are even called.\r\n\r\nSo either there is code missing or the app is crashing from something completely unrelated.\r\n\r\nYou need to look in the Logcat and see what errors you see.  The crash will tell you exactly what Exception occurred and which line of your code it happened on.\r\nraddevus"]},
{"question": "Android studio only shows one button! !", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Any XML attributes prefixed with tools are removed when the app is compiled and are only rendered by Android Studio layout editor.\r\n\r\nYou need to properly set constraints in your ConstraintLayout, not use absolute positioning.\r\n\r\nOr you may instead use RelativeLayout, LinearLayout, etc.\r\n\r\nThe problem is that your views are not properly constrained (basically they aren't linked to anything so when you run your app it doesn't know where to place them and just defaults to the upper left).\r\n\r\nSolution 1 - Right Click on you Layout and select \"Convert View\" Option. then select \"LinearLayout\" Option. it will show all three buttons in the output.\r\n\r\nOtherwise read about Constraints , once you use the guidelines, your buttons will display correctly.\r\n\r\nEDIT: As was rightly pointed out by David Crow, the width is set to the same as their parent causing buttons to overlap and lay on top of each other.\r\nAndre Oosthuizen7-Jul-20 8:15amConstraintLayout7-Jul-20 8:53am7-Jul-20 8:56am7-Jul-20 8:50am7-Jul-20 9:29am", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Bro u are unable to see ur buttons because u have given \"horizontal\" to ur android:orientation=\"Horizontal\"\r\nU just copy this code and paste it to ur xml file\r\n\r\n<?xml version=\"1.0\" encoding=\"utf-8\"?>\r\n\r\n<LinearLayout xmlns:android=\"http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android\"\r\n    xmlns:tools=\"http://schemas.android.com/tools\"\r\n    android:layout_width=\"match_parent\"\r\n    android:layout_height=\"match_parent\"\r\n    android:orientation=\"vertical\">\r\n\r\n    <Button\r\n        android:id=\"@+id/button3\"\r\n        style=\"?android:attr/borderlessButtonStyle\"\r\n        android:layout_width=\"match_parent\"\r\n        android:layout_height=\"wrap_content\"\r\n        android:text=\"strBtn3\" />\r\n\r\n    <Button\r\n        android:id=\"@+id/button2\"\r\n        style=\"?android:attr/borderlessButtonStyle\"\r\n        android:layout_width=\"match_parent\"\r\n        android:layout_height=\"wrap_content\"\r\n        android:text=\"strBtn2\" />\r\n\r\n    <Button\r\n        android:id=\"@+id/button1\"\r\n        style=\"?android:attr/borderlessButtonStyle\"\r\n        android:layout_width=\"match_parent\"\r\n        android:layout_height=\"wrap_content\"\r\n        android:text=\"strBtn1\" />\r\n    <Button\r\n        android:id=\"@+id/button4\"\r\n        style=\"?android:attr/borderlessButtonStyle\"\r\n        android:layout_width=\"match_parent\"\r\n        android:layout_height=\"wrap_content\"\r\n        android:text=\"strBtn4\" />\r\n</LinearLayout>\r\nMember 14883729"]},
{"question": "How to show processes running in android programmatically?", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    []\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nSee this link\r\nAwesome Sohel15-Mar-15 1:52am", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    \r\n\r\nI found this library which may support android devices for versions 6 and below.\r\n\r\n[]\r\n\r\nSee if this helps.\r\nPlease share if you find any other simplified solutions.\r\nGaneshRfromSpace", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    We get the output of the command and return the String. process.waitFor() is used to wait for the command to finish executing.\r\n\r\n\r\ntry {\r\n\tProcess process = Runtime.getRuntime().exec(\"/system/bin/ps\");\r\n\tInputStreamReader reader = new InputStreamReader(process.getInputStream());\r\n\tBufferedReader bufferedReader = new BufferedReader(reader);\r\n\tint numRead;\r\n\tchar[] buffer = new char[5000];\r\n\tStringBuffer commandOutput = new StringBuffer();\r\n\twhile ((numRead = bufferedReader.read(buffer)) > 0) {\r\n\t\tcommandOutput.append(buffer, 0, numRead);\r\n    }\r\n    bufferedReader.close();\r\n    process.waitFor();\r\n\r\n    return commandOutput.toString();\r\n} catch (IOException e) {\r\n    throw new RuntimeException(e);\r\n} catch (InterruptedException e) {\r\n    throw new RuntimeException(e);\r\n}\r\nMember 15023251"]},
{"question": "Android's super folder for windows 10", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    I know of none, but this is not a development question, and this is a dev site: you need to try somewhere dedicated to the OS rather than creating software.\r\n\r\nTry here for starters: [] \r\nBut google will find you many more.\r\nOriginalGriff", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Maybe this one: []\r\nRickZeeland"]},
{"question": "How to delete a file android", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    Seems you just create a variable that has a method call. \r\n\r\nTry:\r\nFile file = new File(path);\r\nfile.delete();\r\n\r\nif(file.exists()){\r\n      file.getCanonicalFile().delete();\r\n      if(file.exists()){\r\n           getApplicationContext().deleteFile(file.getName());\r\n           Toast.makeText(this, \"File deleted.\", Toast.LENGTH_SHORT).show();\r\n      }\r\n}\r\nReference: []\r\n19-Aug-20 16:22pm"]},
{"question": "Save house location ( android studio )", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    We are more than willing to help those that are stuck: but that doesn't mean that we are here to do it all for you! We can't do all the work, you are either getting paid for this, or it's part of your grades and it wouldn't be at all fair for us to do it all for you.\r\n\r\nSo we need you to do the work, and we will help you when you get stuck. That doesn't mean we will give you a step by step solution you can hand in!\r\nStart by explaining where you are at the moment, and what the next step in the process is. Then tell us what you have tried to get that next step working, and what happened when you did.\r\n\r\nIf you are having problems getting started at all, then this may help: []\r\nOriginalGriff"]},
{"question": "How to show processes running in android programmatically?", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    []\r\n\r\n\r\n\r\nSee this link\r\nAwesome Sohel15-Mar-15 1:52am", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    \r\n\r\nI found this library which may support android devices for versions 6 and below.\r\n\r\n[]\r\n\r\nSee if this helps.\r\nPlease share if you find any other simplified solutions.\r\nGaneshRfromSpace", "\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    We get the output of the command and return the String. process.waitFor() is used to wait for the command to finish executing.\r\n\r\n\r\ntry {\r\n\tProcess process = Runtime.getRuntime().exec(\"/system/bin/ps\");\r\n\tInputStreamReader reader = new InputStreamReader(process.getInputStream());\r\n\tBufferedReader bufferedReader = new BufferedReader(reader);\r\n\tint numRead;\r\n\tchar[] buffer = new char[5000];\r\n\tStringBuffer commandOutput = new StringBuffer();\r\n\twhile ((numRead = bufferedReader.read(buffer)) > 0) {\r\n\t\tcommandOutput.append(buffer, 0, numRead);\r\n    }\r\n    bufferedReader.close();\r\n    process.waitFor();\r\n\r\n    return commandOutput.toString();\r\n} catch (IOException e) {\r\n    throw new RuntimeException(e);\r\n} catch (InterruptedException e) {\r\n    throw new RuntimeException(e);\r\n}\r\nMember 15023251"]},
{"question": "Array of edittext android", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    EditText[] t;\r\nt[0].setVisibility(View.VISIBLE);\r\nt[1].setVisibility(View.VISIBLE);\r\nYou have created the array t, but it does not contain anything. So t[0], t[1] etc. do not exist. You must add references to actual EditText items in each entry that you are trying to use. Something like:\r\nEditText[] t = new EditText[6];\r\nt[0] = new EditText;\r\nt[0].setVisibility(View.VISIBLE);\r\nRichard MacCutchan23-Sep-20 7:40am23-Sep-20 8:54am"]},
{"question": "Array of edittext android", "answers": ["\r\n\t\t        \r\n\t\t        \r\n\t        \r\n    EditText[] t;\r\nt[0].setVisibility(View.VISIBLE);\r\nt[1].setVisibility(View.VISIBLE);\r\nYou have created the array t, but it does not contain anything. So t[0], t[1] etc. do not exist. You must add references to actual EditText items in each entry that you are trying to use. Something like:\r\nEditText[] t = new EditText[6];\r\nt[0] = new EditText;\r\nt[0].setVisibility(View.VISIBLE);\r\nRichard MacCutchan23-Sep-20 7:40am23-Sep-20 8:54am"]}
]